1) Most valuable trait in a prospective Valentine:
1) Is your Stat 104 TF. 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0
2) Loves to listen to you vent about how you only got 3 hours of sleep because you had 2 papers, 3 psets, an intramural unicycle juggling meet and psych professor who won't reschedule the midterm even though it conflicts with your PBHA outing. 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 -1 0 0 0 1
3) Lives your entryway. 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0
4) Varsity athlete 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
5) Can sort a list in O(n) 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0

2) Who or what gives worse directions?
(A) Apple Maps 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
(B) My Significant Other 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 -1 0 0 0 0
C) The Gov 1310 Collaboration Policy 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0
D) Ikea assembly manual 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1
E) Pre-term planning 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0

3) Which movie best describes your love life?
A) Avengers - Lots of people involved and explosions all over the place 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 0
B) Hunger Games- A constant battle for survivial 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
C) Twilight - My boyfriend wants to eat me. 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0
D) Skyfall - Shaken not Stirred 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0
E) Dark Knight Rises- Tight, black suits and an old man named Alfred 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0

4) One tequila, two tequila, three tequila:
1) More 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
2) Is a great warmup for my 10am EC class 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0
3) I prefer 0 indexed lists 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
4) Is the prefered method of courtship at the Delphic 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0
5) Nice try, DAPA 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1

5) Biggest lie that gets you through the day:
1) I want to go to med school. 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0
2) Consulting is a really meaningful and fufilling career path. 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0
3) I'll study for this test tomorrow. -1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 -1 0 0
4) Wow, this HUDS glazed acorn squash is delish! 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
5) She/He is just too busy to be in a relationship. 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0

6) How will you be spending the upcoming summer?
1) Curing 3 varities of Liposarcoma cancer found in a
small colony of Capuchin Monkeys native to the
Amazon rainforest in southern Guyana. 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0
2) Convincing your parents that the rigor of your
Comparative Study of Religion cirriculum will make
you a desirable candidate in any job market. 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0
3) At Facebook, where you will spend sleepness nights figuring out whether shifting the like button by one pixel to the left causes a 3% increase in likes. 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0
4) Serving cappuccinos are starbucks. 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1
5) Serving cappuccinos at your JP Morgan internship. 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1

7) How far is long distance?
A) Quad 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
B) Canada 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
C) 5k 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
D) Love transcends all time and space, obliterating the geographic boundaries that seperate hearts. 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0
E) Directly proportional to hotness 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0

8) What house/dorm best describes your ideal partner?
1) Adams - Exclusive access 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0
2) Winthrop - A lion in bed 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 -1
3) Leverett - Energizer bunny 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
4) Pennypacker - Where are you? 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1
5) DeWolfe - Shared by everybody 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 -1

9) Which phone released this year best describes your interaction with the opposite sex?
A) Blackberry - An experienced partner. 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0
B) IPhone 5 - Siri, make me a sandwich. 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
C) Galaxy S3 - Getting into lawsuits. 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0
D) Galaxy Note - Bigger is better. 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0
E) Windows Phone - Try hard, Achieve little 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0

10) Class that best describes your relationship history:
1) HEB 1366: Mating Strategies 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0
2) ENGLISH 90sv: Sexing Victorian Fiction 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0
3) HIST 79j: The Oldest Profession? A Global History
of Sex Work 1750 to the Present 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0
2) GOV 94sl: Cycles of War and Peace 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0
5) VES 163t: The Art of Forgetting 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1

11) The Crimson reports that SEAS is moving to Allston. Your thoughts?
1) Will David Malan still teach in Sanders? If so, I don't care. 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
2) Good riddance. You dorks can take your "practical, real-world skills" over to the Vo-Tech that is HBS, or the Vo-Tech down the river that is TIM spelled
backwards. 0 1 0 0 -1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0
3) SEAS? -1 0 0 0 -1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
4) Surely Everybody Allstons Soon 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0
5) O, I hope somebody provides me with a Caml to use to make the commute. 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0

12) What's your preferred concentration for dating?
1) MCB. Frustrated in lab all day means sexually frustrated at night for me. Win win. 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0
2) Physics. Ever hear of the Big Bang? 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 -1
3) Statistics. I like someone who'll be able to understand just how many sigmas above average I am in bed. 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
4) Computer Science. I figure that between Gates and Zuckerberg, the odds are in my favor for a rich future. 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
5) Linguistics. "Lengua" means tongue in Spanish.Catch my drift? 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0

13) The best thing that Curiosity could find on Mars is:
1) Your future spouse 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0
2) A rusted, 1x2cm metal fragment resembling Harvard style metallurgy dating from 1666-1667. Or it might have just been a smooth rock. 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
3) Your dignity 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 -1 0 0 0 0
4) Waldo 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
5) A completed problem set 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1

14) Proudest achievement of your first semester.
1) Didn't get caught. 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0
2) Facebook friends with David Malan. 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
3) Took the T past Kendall square 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 2
4) Getting n+1 housing in Dunster 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
5) Skipped class. -1 1 0 0 -1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0

15) Kinkiest thing you own:
1) Binder full of women 0 0 1 0 0 2 0 0 1 0 0 0
2) Lock of your TF's hair. 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0
3) Jailbroken TI-83 calculator 0 0 0 -1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
4) 50 shades of grey collector's edition. 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0
5) Munch membership card. 0 0 0 2 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 -1

16) Where were you during the Cambridge blackout?
1) Blacked out -1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
2) Huddling in a corner, suffering from intense withdrawl 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
3) Romantic pset date by candle light 0 0 0 0 1 0 2 1 0 0 1 0
4) Quad, far from the fun 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
5) Widener Stacks 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0

17) Flavor of love:
1) Chocolate covered strawberries 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 -1 1
2) Bacardi 151 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 -1
3) Latex 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0
4) n-Butyllithium 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
5) I love that show! -1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0

18) What is the language of love?
(A) French - Voulez-vous coucher avec moi? ce soir? 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0
(B) C - void love() { love(); } 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0
(C) Klingon - Hab SoSlI' Quch! 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
(D) 한국의 - 난 살과 한국 바베큐를 위해 죽을. 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0
(E) Wingdings2 - 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0

19) If Harvard had a mascot it would be:
1) John Harvard 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
2) Socially Awkward Penguin 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 -2 0 0 0 0
3) RGB: 201, 0, 22 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0
4) Mark Zuckerberg 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 -1 0 0 0 0
5) Goldman Sachs recruiter 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 2 0 1

20) Most important discovery of 2012?
(1) Higgs Boson 0 0 0 0 2 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
(2) You can't buy used textbooks at the Dudley Co-op 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
(3) Water on Mars 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
(4) Gangnam Style 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0
(5) The value of taking a language class that matches your TF's native tongue. 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0

21) Lance Armstrong's secret doping formula:
1) Tears of premeds 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0
2) Four Loko, pre ban 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
3) Three measures of fluxweed, two bundles of knotgrass, stir three times, clockwise. 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0
4) That 3-week old sandwich you forgot in your backpack from Flyby. 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0
5) The blood of a virgin centaur. 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0

22) Your famous last words:
1) [to highschool sweetheart] Once we adopt a regular Skype schedule, we won't even notice it's long distance! 1 0 1 0 0 0 2 1 0 1 0 0
2) [el gato rojo] I dunno man. I just don't think I can justify spending an extra $73 on my moleskine just because it's made of organically grown Bolivian hemp and stitched by blind Tibetan monks. 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0
4) [new haven] Wow, this seems like a very safe and welcoming neighborhood! 0 0 1 0 2 0 0 1 0 0 0 0
3) [bedroom] Oops. 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
5) [your sister's gymnastics meet] YOLO 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 2 1 0 0

23) If you were an Avenger you would be:
A) Hulk - because steroids beats going to the gym 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
B) Hawkeye - 'cause you enjoy bird watching 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
C) Captain America - you look great in spandex 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
D) Thor - because you're getting hammered this weekend 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
E) Black Widow - I like women. 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0

24) Which app best describes your first time?
1) Snapchat: Only three seconds long. 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
2) Fruit Ninja: A fruitbasket, 60 seconds of excitement and a flurry of confused emotions. 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
3) Angry Birds: Birds and the ... pigs? 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
4) App Store: Only 99 cents. 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0
5) Piazza: Ask. Answer. Explore. Whenever. 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0

25) Sexiest pick up line:
1) I'll sanitize your input if you dereference my pointer. 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0
2) Can I buy you a gin and tectonics? 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0
3) You can go ahead and analyze the sample, you'll find my p-value sufficiently large. 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
4) Have you ever bonded via SN2? My strong nucleophile does a mean backside attack. 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0
5) I bet if Jefferson had met you he would have vetoed the Non-Intercourse Act. 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0

26) It's night before Valentine's Day and you don't have a date. You:
1) Reactivate your OKCupid account. 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0
2) Go back to finishing your pset. "There's always next year," says a reassuring voice in your head as you hold back tears. -1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 -1 0 2
3) Go to CVS and buy chocolate. Lots of chocolate. 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1
4) Drunk dial your ex. 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0
5) Finish filling out Datamatch! Duh! 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0

27) What is most likely to make you go to lecture?
(A) Professor breaks out randomly into Gangnam Style 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0
(B) Your crush 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0
(C) 10% class participation 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
(D) Going to lecture is for freshmen -1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0
(E) Midterm 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 -1 0 1

28) Hey...
A) Sexy Lady 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
B) I just met you, and this is crazy 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0
C) Macklemore! Can we go thrift shopping? 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0
D) Jude 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1
E) Ya! 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0

29) I'm never going to _______________ .
(A) Sleep 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1
(B) Finish my thesis 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0
(C) Find love. #foreveralone 0 1 0 0 0 0 -1 -1 0 -1 0 1
(D) Give you up [[rickroll]] 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 -1 0 1 0 -1
(E) Yale 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 -1 0

30) The answer to this question...
1) lies within 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0
2) is too Meta 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1
3) transcends the inquisitory duality, thereby
deconstructing itself. 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0
4) angers me 0 1 0 0 -1 0 0 -1 0 0 0 0
5) 42 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0